TRACY QUICK

FULL STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

M 0416008457

tlquick999@gmail.com



Kings Langley, NSW



Portfolio

PROFILE

Software Engineer: 8 years full time, 15 years part time Experience in multiple languages: Java, JavaScript, Python, C++ Cloud experience with AWS, Render and Netlify Strong interest in DevOps, experience using **Docker** and **Jenkins** Enjoys learning new technologies

EXPERIENCE

Jun 2021 - Sept 2022

Academic Coordinator - Programming at UTSCollege

- Developed, managed and taught 3 subjects (Java and Python), developing 6-12 full SDLC Java projects each year (like Chess)
- Provided regular feedback on code quality for up to 200 students
- Teaching Innovation Award recipient 2021

Feb 2007 - Jun 2021

Subject Coordinator – Programming at UTS:Insearch

- Developed, managed and taught 2 programming subjects (Java)
- Taught 5 other IT subjects networking, web systems, business requirements modelling and databases
- Championed best practices in programming pedagogy
- Scaffolded exercises and tasks, pushing pass rates over 90%
- Engaged in continuous learning, research and upskilling
- Teaching Innovation Award recipient 2014, 2018

Mar 1997 - Dec 2005

(Senior) Software Engineer at MYOB/Solution6/Xlon/CeeData

- Full SDLC (monolith) using C++, C, Java, VB and some C#
- Mentoring juniors, reviewing code for adherence to guidelines
- Specifying 1500 pages of elaborated use cases for new product suite (MYOB Assets)
- Provided sole 3rd level support for a product suite
- Youngest Senior Software Engineer ever promoted at CeeData

REFERENCES

Program Manager – IT and Business, UTSCollege, Sydney

Contact details can be made available on request

KEY SKILLS

- Java: Core 8/11
- Spring: Core, MVC, Cloud, JPA, Hibernate, Thymeleaf
- Spring Boot: TomCat, Jetty
- JavaScript: React, Express, **NodeJS**
- Databases: Postgres, MongoDB
- AWS: EC2, S3, Dynamo, IAM, VPC, CloudFormation, Lambda, **API** Gateway
- CI/CD: Docker, Jenkins, K8s

CERTIFICATES

Spring Framework DevOps on AWS Agile with Atlassian Jira Kubernetes Crash Course (studying)

EDUCATION

Johns Hopkins University, online Introduction to DevSecOps Completed 2022

Cisco Systems, Sydney **CCNA1** Instructor Graduated 2014

Macquarie University, Sydney **Bachelor of Science**

Maths, Computing, Physics, Geophysics Graduated 1996